getstudyroom.com 2017-02-05

# StudyRoom

Last revised on January 28, 2013

StudyRoom recognizes that your privacy is very important and take it seriously. This Privacy Policy describes StudyRoom's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the StudyRoom Service, via the StudyRoom website, your mobile phone, or through StudyRoom's applications for mobile devices (e.g., the StudyRoom iPhone application). We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service.

## Information Collection and Use

StudyRoom uses information we collect to analyze how the Service is used, diagnose service or technical problems, maintain security, personalize content, remember information to help you efficiently access your account, monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns, and track User Content and users as necessary to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

### User-Provided Information

When you register for a member account with the Service, you will provide us information about yourself, such as your name and email address. If you create a profile, certain member information, including without limitation your name, groups, school and any additional content that you submit on your profile will be displayed to other users at your school or in your groups to facilitate user interaction within our services.

We may use your email address to send you Service-related notices (including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail). You can control receipt of certain Service-related messages on your Account/Email Settings page. We may also use your contact information to send you marketing email messages. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

By choosing to sign on to the Service through Facebook or another third-party service, you give us permission to access and use your information from that service as permitted by that service, and to store your log-in credentials for that service.

You also provide us information in User Content you post to the Service. Your questions, answers, and other contributions on the Service, and metadata about them (such as when you posted them), are publicly viewable on the Service, along with your name (unless the Service permits you to post anonymously). This information may be searched by search engines and be republished elsewhere on the Web in accordance with our Terms of Service.

Other users may provide us with your name, email address, and other information when inviting you to a class or other group on the Service. If you join a group or class, you may also provide us with course information, including instructor information, syllabus, homework and lecture notes. If you choose to invite others in a class or group on the Service, we will ask you for some information and send an email invitation. StudyRoom does not store this information when sending invitations, we use a custom and unique random generated code system to track if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of the invitation.

Any content you upload to your profile, along with any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by others. If you want to delete or disable your profile, please contact us at connect@getstudyroom.com.

### Information Collected Automatically

When you use the Service, we use persistent and session cookies and other tracking technologies to: (a) store your username and password; (b) analyze the usage of the Service; (c) customize the Service to your preferences; and (d) enhance your navigation through the site. A persistent cookie remains on your computer after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

We may also use other Internet technologies, log files, clear GIFs, Flash technologies, and other similar technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and track your use of the Service. We also may include clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to determine whether the message has been opened. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather additional information through other methods.

We use these automated technologies to collect and analyze certain types of information we consider to be non-personal information, including: (a) information related to the devices you use to access or interact with the Service, such as: IP addresses, unique device identifiers and other information about your mobile phone or other mobile device(s), browser types, browser language; and (b) information related to the ways in which you interact with the Service, such as: referring and exit pages and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time you used the Service, and other similar information. We may also capture other data, such as search criteria and results.

StudyRoom discloses a subset of this automatically collected information. Specifically, you consent to StudyRoom's disclosure of information related to the ways in which you interact with the Service, such as: landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages (including questions and answers viewed), the date and time you used the Service, and other similar information on the Service to other users, along with your name and profile.

## How We Share Your Information

### Personally Identifiable Information

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service. StudyRoom may share your personally identifiable information with third parties for the purpose of providing the Service to you. If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of StudyRoom (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

StudyRoom may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect StudyRoom's rights or property.

From time to time, we may run contests, advertisements, special offers, or other events or activities ("Events") on the Service together with a third party partner. If you provide information to such third parties, you give them permission to use it for the purpose of that Event and any other use that you approve. We cannot control third parties' use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in these Events.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information:

We may aggregate and/or anonymize information collected through the Service so that the information does not identify you. We may use aggregated, anonymized, and other non-personally identifiable information for any purpose, including for research and marketing purposes, and our use and disclosure of such information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy.

## How We Protect Your Information

StudyRoom uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to StudyRoom or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, StudyRoom will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## Your Choices About Your Information

You may decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Service, in which case StudyRoom may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to your account and going to your "Account/Email Settings" page. You can review and correct the information about you that StudyRoom keeps on file by contacting us directly at connect@getstudyroom.com.

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. StudyRoom does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register with the Service. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will remove that information.

## Links to Other Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personally identifiable information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the types of personally identifiable information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request in an email to connect@getstudyroom.com.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or StudyRoom’s practices, please contact us at connect@getstudyroom.com.
